Life blooms like a flower
생명은 꽂처럼
咲き誇る命の花
生命如花朵綻放
生命如花朵绽放
Far away or by the road
멀리 혹은 길가에 피어나
遠くて近くに
或許遙遠，或許就在路邊
或许遥远，或许就在路边
Waiting for the one
그 자람을 기다리며
君のことを待ち続け
等待著那個人
等待着那个人
To find the way back home
돌아가는 길을 찾아
拠り所へ導くよ
找到回歸的路
找到回家的路
Rain falls a thousand times
수 천 번외 비에 씻겨
絶えることない雨の中
雨水數千次的沖刷
雨水数千次的冲刷
No footprints of come-and-go
오고 가는 발자국은 이미 사라졌네
行き交う足跡も消え去る
已經分辨不清來往的腳印
已经分辨不清来往的脚印
You who once went by
이곳을 지나던 그대
この場所に居た君も
曾經過此處的你
曾经过此处的你
Where will you belong
어디에 속할 것인가
いずれは何処に往くのだろう
終將屬於哪裡
终将属于哪里
I feel your sigh and breath
바람에 실린 마지막 울부짖음 속
君のため息も呼吸も
我察覺到你的嘆息與呼吸
我察觉到你的叹息与呼吸
In the last blow of wind
당신의 한숨과 숨결이 느껴져
風の吐息と共に私に触れる
在風最後的呼嘯之中
在风最后的呼啸之中
Not yet for the story on the last page
마지막 장의 이야기는 시작하지 않았기에
まだまだ続く私たちの物語
還未到將故事翻至末頁的時候
还未到将故事翻至末页的时候
It's not the end
아직 모든 게 끝난 게 아니야
次のページを描いていこう
所以一切還未結束
所以一切还未结束
Life blooms like a flower
생명은 꽂처럼
咲き誇る命の花
生命如花朵綻放
生命如花朵绽放
Far away or by the road
멀리 혹은 길가에 피어나
遠くて近くに
或許遙遠，或許就在路邊
遥不可及，或触手可得
Waiting for the one
그 자람을 기다리며
君のことを待ち続け
等待著那個人
等待着那个人
To find the way back home
돌아가는 길을 찾아
拠り所へ導くよ
找到回歸的路
找到回家的路
Time flows across the world
시간은 세계를 가로지르고
浮世の歳月が流れ
時光流淌過天地間
时光流淌过天地间
There is always a longer way to go
내 여정은 끝니지 않겠지
終わらない私の旅路
我的旅程不會結束
我的旅程不会结束
Till I reach your arms
당신의 품에 닿을 때까지
君を抱き締める
直至能與你相擁
直至能与你相拥
A madder there for you
그대의 바보가 될게
一枝のアカネを捧げるまで
並獻上一株茜草
并献上一株茜草
Up against the stream
개울을 거슬러 올라가다 보면
川の流れを遡り
沿著溪流向上
沿着溪流向上
Waterways will join as one
무수한 물길도 하나로 합쳐지겠지
澪はやがて一つに繋がる
無數水流終將合一
无数水流终将合一
Tracing to the source
뿌리를 쫒을 때
根源にたどり着いた頃には
追溯著源頭
追溯着源头
No more strayed or lost
더는 길을 잃지 않아
迷いも戸惑いもなくなる
便可不再迷惘
You will see petals fly
꽂잎이 흩날리는 게 보인다면
花吹雪が目に映り
你將看見花瓣紛飛
你将看见花瓣纷飞
When lament becomes carol
슬픔의 소리가 송가가 될 때
挽歌が讚歌に変わる時
將悲傷之音轉而歌頌
当悲伤之音转而歌颂
Could you please hear my voice
내 목소리를 들어줘
私の呼びがけに応えて
請你聽見我的聲音
请你听见我的声音
That hungers for a duo
당신과 함께 노래하고 싶어
君と二重唱を奏でよう
正渴望與你二重唱
正渴望与你二重唱
Life blooms like a flower
생명은 꽂처럼
咲き誇る命の花
生命如花朵綻放
生命如花朵绽放
Far away or by the road
멀리 혹은 길가에 피어나
遠くて近くに
或許遙遠，或許就在路邊
或许遥远，或许就在路边
Waiting for the one
그 자람을 기다리며
君のことを待ち続け
等待著那個人
等待着那个人
To find the way back home
돌아가는 길을 찾아
拠り所へ導くよ
找到回歸的路
找到回家的路
Time flows across the world
시간은 세계를 가로지르고
浮世の歳月が流れ
時光流淌過天地間
时光流淌过天地间
There is always a longer way to go
내 여정은 끝니지 않겠지
終わらない私の旅路
我的旅程不會結束
我的旅程不会结束
Till I reach your arms
당신의 품에 닿을 때까지
君を抱き締める
直至能與你相擁
直至能与你相拥
A madder there for you
그대의 바보가 될게
一枝のアカネを捧げるまで
並獻上一株茜草
并献上一株茜草
Life blooms like a flower
생명은 꽂처럼
咲き誇る命の花
生命如花朵綻放
生命如花朵绽放
Far away or by the road
멀리 혹은 길가에 피어나
遠くて近くに
或許遙遠，或許就在路邊
或许遥远，或许就在路边
Waiting for the one
그 자람을 기다리며
君のことを待ち続け
等待著那個人
等待着那个人
To find the way back home
돌아가는 길을 찾아
拠り所へ導くよ
找到回歸的路
找到回家的路
Time flows across the world
시간은 세계를 가로지르고
浮世の歳月が流れ
時光流淌過天地間
时光流淌过天地间
There is always a longer way to go
내 여정은 끝니지 않겠지
終わらない私の旅路
我的旅程不會結束
我的旅程不会结束
Till I reach your arms
당신의 품에 닿을 때까지
君を抱き締める
直至能與你相擁
直至能与你相拥
A madder there for you
그대의 바보가 될게
一枝のアカネを捧げるまで
並獻上一株茜草
并献上一株茜草